回话 能听到吗 能听到吗 探险小队？
Come in. Do you read me? Are you reading, landing team?
能 我们听到了 你能听到吗？
Yes, we read you. Can you hear me?
听到了 听到了
We hear you. We hear you.
契约号 我们需要支援
Covenant, we need help.
我们有人员伤亡 需要立刻撤离此地
We've had casualties. We need immediate evacuation.
重复一遍 我们需要立刻撤离
I repeat, immediate evacuation.
人员伤亡
Casualties?
他们是说有人员伤亡吗
Did he say "we have casualties"?
老妈 把飞船下降到风暴上空四十公里
Mother, bring us within 40 km's of the storm.
- 长官 - 很抱歉
- Sir! - I am sorry.
该命令会让飞船船体承受过高负荷
That order would exceed structural tolerance.
强制执行命令 田纳西04983
Command override. Tennessee 0-4-9-8-3.
我无法执行任何可能
I am unable to comply with any order
引起飞船系统遭受灾难性损坏的命令
that would result in catastrophic system failure.